axappphealthcare.co.uk 2019-05-23

# Privacy policy - AXA PPP healthcare

Here is a summary of our data privacy notice. If you would like to read the full notice you can find it on the AXA UK website at [www.axa.co.uk/privacy-policy](http://www.axa.co.uk/privacy-policy "AXA UK Privacy Policy").

We want to reassure you we never sell personal member information to third parties. We will only use your information in ways we are allowed to by law, which includes only collecting as much information as we need. We will get your consent to process information such as your medical information when it's necessary to do so.

We get information about you and any family members from you, those family members, your healthcare providers, your employer (if you are on a company scheme), your insurance broker if you have one and third party suppliers of information, such as credit reference agencies. We get this information when you apply for or purchase products or services, when you claim or use our services, when you fill out surveys or feedback forms or when we do customer research / analysis..

If you have access to a product or service we process your information mainly for managing that product / service, including investigating fraud. We also have a legal obligation to do things such as report suspected crime to law enforcement agencies. We also do some processing because it helps us run our business, such as research, finding out more about you and statistical analysis for example to help us decide on premiums and marketing.

We may disclose your information to other people or organisations. For example we'll do this to:

  * manage your claims/services, e.g. to deal with your doctors or any reinsurers
  * manage your policy with your insurance broker;
  * facilitate access to the Doctor@Hand service, provided by Doctor Care Anywhere;
  * help us reclaim claims costs if your claim relates to an injury caused by a third party (we use external law firms to help us with this)  
  * help us prevent and detect crime and medical malpractice by talking to other insurers and relevant agencies; and
  * allow other AXA companies in the UK to contact you if you have agreed.

Where our using your information relies on your consent you can withdraw your consent, but if you do we may not be able to process your claims or manage your plan properly. In some cases you have the right to ask us to stop processing your information or tell us that you don't want to receive certain information from us, such as marketing communications. You can also ask us for a copy of information we hold about you and ask us to correct information that is wrong.

If you want to exercise any of your rights you can do so by contacting the Data Protection Officer in writing at:   
AXA PPP Healthcare Ltd, Jubilee House, Vale Road, Tunbridge Wells, Kent, TN1 1BJ

## Errors & Omissions

If you believe that there may be an error in any of the information that you have submitted via this website, please email: [webmaster@axa-ppp.co.uk](mailto:webmaster@axa-ppp.co.uk). We will review your records as soon as possible.

## Information about Children

We do not intentionally collect any information via this website from children under 16 years of age, and unless the information was collected in connection with a policy claim, shall delete the details when a parent or guardian notifies us that details have been obtained from their child.

## Additional Information

We will amend this privacy statement from time to time and for this reason, it is valid for a period of 1 day from the date you have viewed it. We recommend that you read this statement and the full privacy policy regularly.
